Father, don't drink it!
What?
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Guards!
Summon the imperial physician!
Your Majesty!
Guards! It was you who poisoned it!
What's happening?
It seems A Lan already knows something.
You are actually the third prince of Yunze.
Aren't you?
A Lan is indeed clever.
The third prince of Yunze, Your Majesty?
Weren't you already dead?
You are the one colluding with Prince Ning.
The one hiding in the shadows is also you.
Yuwen Rui and I treated you like family.
Royal Sister was even more devoted, wanting to marry you.
But you...
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
What about me?
When Yunmi burned our Yunze territory years ago,
and wounded our Yunze warriors,
you should have expected this day would come.
What?
Is Yunmi the only one allowed to destroy my homeland?
Am I not allowed to slaughter your Yunmi royal family?
A Lan.
You can't blame me.
Yunze's destruction
was simply its own fault.
Its own fault?
You really know how to twist the truth.
Your Majesty!
Guards! Protect His Majesty!
Guards!
Your Majesty!
This...
What is this?
Your Majesty!
You...
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Father!
Your Majesty! Father! Your Majesty!
Commander He!
Who ordered you to be here?
Step aside!
Fourth Princess.
Please return to your room to rest.
Our master has ordered
that you are not to leave your room.
Who is your master?
Step aside!
Except for His Majesty and the Fifth Princess,
take everyone to Liuyun Hall.
Without my order,
no one is to enter.
Yes!
Move! Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, move!
Hurry up!
Your Majesty!
Move!
Your Majesty! What are you doing?
Your Majesty!
Hurry!
Empress, hurry!
Go!
You...
You really are...
Su Qi, the third prince of Yunze.
Your Majesty actually remembers my name.
When Your Majesty sent troops to attack Yunze years ago,
did you ever think
that over a decade later,
your life and those of the Yunmi royal family
would be in my hands?
The Grand Tutor I trusted without doubt,
and even my palace guards,
are all under your control.
It seems your scheming wasn't just for a day or two.
National and familial hatred
naturally requires careful planning.
Where is the Map of the Nine Provinces and the Secret Key?
Even if I die,
I will not give you the key and the map.
Father! Father!
It seems you won't relent until you see your own coffin.
How about I cripple one of your hands first?
Stop!
Royal Sister!
Whoever dares hurt them, try it!
Father!
A Zi!
A Lan!
You really are Su Qi?
The third prince of Yunze?
A Zi.
I...
Say it.
Are you Yuwen Xiu,
or are you Su Qi?
Yuwen Xiu died long ago.
He was recuperating outside the capital since childhood.
He died of illness when he was eight.
At that time, I was rescued by loyalists.
We found a way to take over Yuwen Xiu's identity.
You hid it quite well.
It's my fault for being so foolish.
I never once doubted you.
I even wanted to grow old together with you.
Release Father and A Lan.
The Map of the Nine Provinces and the Secret Key
are still in your father's hands.
Then...
Draw your sword.
A Zi.
Don't force me.
Royal Sister!
A Zi!
All that carefree attitude,
all that poor martial skill,
it was all fake.
From today onward,
you and I
are like this sword.
From now on,
all ties are severed.
Let go of me!
I will never let you go in this lifetime.
You're insane!
I am indeed insane.
What exactly do you want?
Your father will be safe for now.
Persuade him to hand over the Secret Key and the treasure map quickly.
Otherwise,
all of you will die.
Lock them both in Renxin Hall.
Post guards to watch them closely.
Yes!
Put me down, Royal Sister!
If you dare harm my father and A Lan
I will kill you with my own hands
You stay by my side
We'll be like we always were
I promise not to harm them
Like always
But you are Su Qi
Not Yuwen Xiu
Father
Are you alright?
A Lan
Listen to me
There is a secret passage in the palace
It leads to Zigui Mountain outside the city
What do you want?
Our master is soft-hearted
He won't force you to hand over the map and key
I'm different
If you don't want to get hurt
Hand them over now
I fear if I hand them over
I'll die even sooner
You're not afraid of death
But what about the Fifth Princess?
You!
No need to look at me like that, Fifth Princess
Blame your father
I'll ask one last time
Where are the map and the key?
You scoundrel!
Don't worry about me, Father
Don't you dare regret this
Stop!
Fine
The treasure map and the key
I'll give them to you
Father!
Those things are not as important as you
Take them
Father! Father!
Father...
Finally got them
Sir
Prince Ning has woken up
Just a useless pawn
Him waking up is pointless
Keep watch over them
They are not to leave Renxin Hall
Yes
Oh, right
There's something I forgot to tell the Fifth Princess
Yuwen Rui, on his way to Yu Town...
Died
What did you say?
Why the fuss, Fifth Princess?
If Yuwen Rui hadn't died
How could our plan
have proceeded so smoothly?
With just you people?
You think you could take his life?
In terms of martial skill alone
Our men were no match for him
But who told him to care so much about you?
What do you mean?
We sent someone disguised as you
When he went to save "you"
They stabbed him
Impossible
He wouldn't die
Don't you dare lie to me
This item should look familiar, Fifth Princess
I heard when Yuwen Rui died
He was still clutching this lucky pouch
No...
He can't be dead
He clearly promised
that I should wait for him to return
Father...
He's not dead
Right?
He clearly said
he wanted to grow old together with me
He wouldn't break his promise
No...
This is a protective charm I made for you myself
Wait for me to return
First bow to heaven and earth
Second bow to the parents
Third, husband and wife bow to each other
From now on
you are my wife
The guards say
you refuse to eat anything
A Zi
You're torturing me
You said no matter what happened
you would never regret it
and you would never leave me
Those words were for Yuwen Xiu
Not for you, Su Qi
The only thing I, An Kezi, regret in this life
is meeting you
Your father has already handed over the key and the map
If you promise me
to stay by my side
Once we uncover the map's secret
I can spare them
A Lan
Don't be like this
If you're like this
Beloved Minister Yuwen's spirit in heaven
will not rest in peace
What spirit in heaven?
When a person dies
they're gone
Nothing is left
A Lan
What's wrong with you?
Don't scare me
Don't scare your father
My precious daughter
You must be strong
Father...
Was he really so cruel
to abandon me like this?
Yuwen Rui...
What?
Father!
The window
Look by the window!
What is it?
It's the signal flame he gave me
He's not dead
He didn't die!
You mean...
Beloved Minister Yuwen
He said
if I ever wanted to see him
to use this as a signal
I never thought her arrival
would actually change Yuwen Rui's fate
A Lan
If you want to live
Tell Yuwen Xiu
that I died here
Sir
Will the Fifth Princess understand?
She will.
What's the situation in the palace?
The guards are extremely tight.
Our people can't get in at all.
And we can't gather any information.
Slow down.
Beloved Minister Yuwen must be trying to save us.
By the way, Father.
Didn't you say there's a secret passage outside the palace?
If we can contact Yuwen Rui,
and coordinate with him from inside and out,
we might be able to subdue Su Qi.
Yes.
But now the entire palace is under their control.
This Renxin Hall,
not even a fly can get out.
How can we send a message?
Now we can only rely on Royal Sister.
A Zi.
You should eat something.
Seeing you like this,
I can't eat anything.
Your Highness, it's terrible!
The Fifth Princess, she...
What's wrong with A Lan?
Father!
A Lan, she...
can't accept Beloved Minister Yuwen's death.
Eldest Cousin, he...
Royal Sister.
You're here.
How are you?
Royal Sister.
I'm fine.
Listen to me.
Yuwen Rui is not dead.
A Zi.
These are pastries from Zhenxiu Pavilion I brought for you.
And that Beggar's Chicken from the north of the city.
And this plum wine.
You said before,
at this point,
what's the point of you doing all this?
I just...
want to be good to you.
All these years,
you have indeed been very good to me.
In my palace,
many things were gifts from you.
I've kept them all carefully.
A Zi.
I...
These are all things you gave me on Qixi Festival.
You said,
since I don't often leave the palace,
you wanted to bring all the interesting things
from outside into my palace.
A Zi.
I'm sorry.
Between us,
why did it become like this?
Could it be that everything,
was all fake?
No.
It's not fake.
My feelings for you,
you know better than anyone.
A Zi.
I know you still have me in your heart.
Let's forget those bad memories
and start over, okay?
Does what you said before still count?
As long as we start over,
you'll release Father and the others?
Of course.
As long as you stay by my side,
I'll promise you anything.
Thank you.
A Zi.
Thank you for being willing to give me another chance.
Do you remember our first meeting?
I had just returned to the capital then.
I entered the palace to visit Her Majesty the Empress.
You took me around the palace,
secretly releasing blessing lanterns.
We almost set the Imperial Garden on fire.
Back then, we could play without restraint.
But now,
with national and familial hatred,
can we ever go back to how it was?
We can.
We definitely can.
A Zi.
We still have a long life ahead.
All those beautiful moments from the past,
let's experience them together again.
I wonder how A Zi is doing.
Don't worry, Father.
I've already told Royal Sister the method.
She will definitely succeed.
You're here.
This one is almost finished.
I remember back then,
we both drew on the sky lantern, right?
You mean...
Eldest Cousin faked his death?
What should I do?
Right now,
you must not oppose Su Qi.
You need to lower his guard against you.
Make him truly believe
that you've completely given up struggling.
When he relaxes his vigilance,
then you send this out.
A sky lantern.
When Yuwen Rui sees it,
he will surely understand.
I'll release this one myself.
You make another one.
Okay.
Let's make it together.
A Zi.
This is the happiest moment
of my life.
Sir.
There was no unusual activity in the palace today.
It's just that moments ago inside the palace,
it seemed someone was releasing sky lanterns.
Sky lanterns?
Who would be releasing sky lanterns in the palace at this time?
Shoot down all the sky lanterns.
Yes.
Father!
I just saw the sky lanterns rise.
Su Qi indeed believed A Zi.
Sir.
These sky lanterns have nothing special about them.
Send people to Zigui Mountain to search for the secret passage.
I'm going to the Meng residence.
Yes.